To get you signed up and retired as a
Viking. Yeah, let's do it. For fun, we
actually have your your original
contract. Oh, wow. That's crazy. Is this
your original contract? So, this guy
That's the original, huh? This is the
contract your dad signed like 13 like 14
years ago, whatever it's been.
Look at that, guys. That's super cool.
Oh, wow.
>> [laughter]
>> Oh, wow. Look at that, guys. How cool is
that?
Well, that'll go in our house. That is
so cool. Thank you. Yeah.
What?
How do they know your name? All right,
you think you guys still think I should
retire? Yeah.
>> [laughter]
>> It's your last chance.
>> The player you are, everybody knows. You
know, team captain, [music] Walter
Payton Man of the Year, locker room
leader. There's never going to be
another Adam Thielen.
Appreciate you. Yes, sir. Yes, sir.
Appreciate you. Congrats. Oh, thank you.